Vengeance is the ultimate weapon.
War is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Philip G. Atwell.
FBI agent Jack Crawford is out for revenge when his partner is killed
and all clues point to the mysterious assassin Rogue.
But when Rogue turns up years later to take care of some unfinished
business, he triggers a violent clash of rival gangs.
Will the truth come out before it's too late?
And when the dust settles, who will remain standing?
Rogue, played by Jet Li.
Special Agent Jack Crawford, played by Jason Statham.
Li Chang, played by John Lone.
Shiro Yanagawa, played by Ryo Ishibashi.
Kira Yanagawa, played by Devon Aoki.
Wu Ti, played by Mark Cheng Ho-Nam.
War is a 2007 American action film directed by Philip G.
Atwell in his directorial debut and featuring stage
combat choreographed by Corey Yuen.
The film stars Jet Li and Jason Statham.
Jason Statham plays an FBI agent determined to take down a mysterious assassin
known as Rogue (played by Jet Li), after his partner is murdered.
War features the second collaboration between Jet Li and Jason Statham,
reuniting them for the first time since 2001 film The One.
War's working title was Rogue; it was changed to avoid
conflict with another film with the same name.
It was re-titled as Rogue Assassin in New Zealand, Japan, Hong Kong, Singapore,
India, Australia, the Philippines and several European countries.
The film was released in the United States on August 24, 2007, receiving negative reviews from
critics and grossed $40.7 million at the box office against the $25 million budget.
The tone is dark and intense.